(Sheldon:)and Bill Nye the Science Guy.
(Sheldon:)'Cause, legally, I'm not allowed to.
(Sheldon:)Oh, and, also,
Carrie Fisher, you know,
'cause I hear she can be pretty nuts.
(Penny:)I can't believe Leonard
is spending hundreds of dollars
(Penny:)on scalped tickets.
(Amy:)Last week, you spent
that on a little dress.
(Penny:)Yeah, but those tickets
only get him into Comic-Con.
(Penny:)That dress gets me
into anywhere I want.
(Bernadette:)Those tickets were pretty expensive.
(Bernadette:)I had to give Howie an advance
on his allowance.
(Bernadette:)Now he's never gonna
put his toys away.
(Amy:)Why can't they do something sensible
(Amy:)like Sheldon and start their
own comic book convention?
(Amy:)Also, who wants
to throw me out that window?
(Bernadette:)While they're acting like teenagers,
we could do something grown-up.
(Amy:)Oh. You mean like a museum?
(Penny:)Yes, like a museum,
but anything else.
(Bernadette:)I know. There's a nice hotel
not far from here